I've obtained one disc. I have it.
He'll come back to life.
I am certain that my father
will definitely regenerate.
How about we call this
Operation Savage Guardian?
You oughta let him tag along.
He'll be a great help.
I forgot to mention, his
name is Weather Forecast.
Jumpin' Jack Spark!
No weather forecast!
Still though, where is that
anti-gravity-wielding thief?
I need to get the disc back!
I can't believe you're a good girl.
I'm not sure if you're in my life.
Please don't let you know.
I'll see you soon.
Okay?
All right? All right!
Get away from!
No more time!
I don't wanna play?
Get more time!
Let's go, go!
1, 2, 3!
Come and find a way!
Fight for me!
Break out! We tell me, you
The abnormality alarm has
been activated in Hallway 7B.
Yes, that's right.
It's Passage 7B.
We're currently confirming the situation.
Did something unusual happen?
We're not certain yet.
However, Passage 7B is only meant
for going to and from the factory.
There's no possibility that
it's a fire or a prisoner riot.
There's no need to worry.
No, I'm not worried.
I maintain the utmost trust in the Green
Dolphin Street Prison and its prisoners.
It was really just quite noisy, so I
got unnecessarily curious and inquired.
You do know that there hasn't
been even one successful
escapee from the Aquarium
in the past 20 years,
correct?
Plus, outside the
passageway is the courtyard.
There won't be anyone trying
to escape from this location.
You're certainly right about that.
We'll handle it.
Thanks, Father.
Right.
Very well, then.
Another quick unnecessary question.
Is that clock hanging up
in the corner accurate?
Yeah, of course it is.
Looks like it's 11.58.
I guess it's almost lunchtime.
At 11.51, there was an outgoing
call to the Speedwagon Foundation.
I've got my usual ask.
I want to listen to this recording, play
the audio of this one outgoing call.
From the women's prison
phone stand number 16.
The call from about seven minutes ago.
Hey weather forecast.
Since you made contact with me, you're
now also controlled by zero gravity.
That weird guy isn't anywhere to be seen.
We need to get the disc back quickly!
Don't panic.
The thief has to be somewhere
inside this wash house.
He must be hiding.
The courtyard's on the
other side of that door.
Your objective lies just
beyond that doorway.
However, the door appears to be locked.
You might need to blast it
away or force it open somehow.
There's a little bit of a problem.
It's sort of hard to say it out loud.
The thing is it's a personal matter.
Although I am at a physical
limit, so I'm troubled.
Um and I don't know why it
became a problem so suddenly.
Uh well but um
I do think it happens to
everyone sometimes hmm.
What are you talking about?
It's like I was saying
It's related to your lower
half begins with you.
It's a biological urge you have
when you're thinking to yourself.
Thank God
It isn't number two.
Oh Do you need to take a piss?
Don't leave me close to say that
It's getting really bad
You would have to do it
somewhere over there.
Oh geez I never should have asked you know
A man, of course.
I already did it myself.
There, just now while floating.
When you find yourself in zero gravity,
the blood in your body will
suddenly collect at your head.
That blood is usually down in the lower
parts of the body because of gravity.
Between your skin and bones is flesh
that's squishy and swollen with blood.
It's called Moonface.
However,
it can be dangerous when too much
blood goes up into your head And thus,
your kidneys automatically begin working
to lessen the amount of blood in you.
That's why there's a
severe diuretic effect.
It removes sodium content through
piss and thins out the blood. Wait!
Hang on a second!
Hey, don't worry.
My clouds will absorb it.
Hey! Hey! This...
This is floating!
What the heck is this?
Why is it spilling out from the clouds?
Hey, look here, weather
forecast! My... my blood!
It's being sucked into the wall's seam!
Shit! Mine too.
It's coming out of my room from earlier.
My nose won't stop bleeding either!
It's gushing! It's so...
so painful.
Slowly.
Could this be...
how I die?
Jolene!
Everything that I make contact
with enters zero gravity.
That means this room itself
has become zero gravity.
Air!
Air doesn't stay put
within a zero gravity zone!
It'll get pulled by the surrounding
gravity and then escape!
We need to fill these gaps in the wall,
or at this rate, we'll suffocate
if we don't seal them quickly!
No, Jolene.
What we really need to worry
about is not suffocation,
but the fact that our
blood will boil and we
will die from that before
we even run out of air.
While within a vacuum, a person's
blood will boil right up like water.
A vacuum with zero gravity makes
one's blood dry up in 20 seconds.
It's quite a long time before the
individual would ever suffocate.
Reloading bullets.
We're gonna get shot.
So come on, Jolene.
Let's hide somewhere.
What are you talking about?
My nose is still bleeding way too much.
We gotta stop the airflow.
Weather forecast.
Take good care not to breathe too heavily.
I collected what little remaining
air was left within this
room and covered our bodies
with clouds in order to trap it.
So this is a cloud suit?
This room is basically a vacuum now.
These clouds hold all the oxygen left.
Your nose, it stopped bleeding.
So how long can we keep on breathing?
I don't want to answer that question,
but probably like two minutes.
It's a cloud suit on the verge of death.
We need to find and defeat
that man during this time.
Otherwise, we'd be thrown into
the vacuum for sure afterwards.
Yes, that's correct.
Now, where is he?
We need to find him, because even if we
don't do anything, he'll still attack us.
Oh, hey.
Now that I'm not bleeding,
something's been bothering me.
Wait, Jolene.
I said two minutes, but
it could only be one.
We need to hurry and focus on finding him.
The carbon dioxide is increasing.
But the laundry hamper, why
isn't that floating as well?
You see that hamper over there?
I've touched the floor, walls, doors,
and even shutters of this room.
That's why the whole chamber
entered into zero gravity,
and now everything is floating.
But then, why are the hamper and
those metal barrels not floating too?
They're attached to the floor instead.
Also our strange foe how is the enemy
possibly breathing inside of this
vacuum Given the circumstances shouldn't
the blood of that freak be boiling up
I see that's his attack range distance his
zero gravity's got a distance range and it
doesn't Extend through
the whole room attack
distance the laundry
hamper has got to be within
20 meters from where we're floating.
Zero gravity ends there.
If we go that way, there will
surely be normal air to breathe.
You gotta go first, Weather Forecast.
He's outside the vacuum.
If you don't get a supply
of oxygen before I do,
there's no way either one
of us can approach him.
I'm inclined to agree.
Outside the hamper.
Go now, Weather Forecast.
The pressure within the cloud
suit is becoming strange you've
got to go right now quit before
the cloud suit flies away.
No way in hell you can
get out of my attack
range you fools he'll
try to shoot him down.
But I won't let him!
I'll do all I can to
guard weather forecast!
That guy's coming around us.
I'm gonna charge!
Let's go!
Weather forecast is going to
reach the oxygen in a few feet.
As soon as my ally gets to that supply
of fresh air, he's going to corner you.
If you want it that
badly, then have some air.
You don't even have to
go to the laundry hamper.
Just a moment ago, I finished my
attack and hit my true target.
I was not attempting to direct the bullets
to hit the man you call weather forecast.
I meant to hit that metal
barrel to damage it.
There's a little bit of air
in the metal barrel, correct?
If I'm right,
then the air inside of
that can is on the brink
of bursting from being
pressurized in a vacuum!
Weather forecast!
He's been pushed back
into the zero gravity.
He's finished now.
Done for.
Your pathetic friend probably can't obtain
enough air power to stop
that momentum anymore.
Oh no! Weather forecast!
It's simply no use.
Cloud suit itself is about to break.
Jolene!
What the heck are you doing?
Go back!
He's going to shoot you!
On top of that, you'll lose
oxygen just from the moving force!
She makes decisions so quickly.
You're trying to stop the Cloud
Guy's movement with your body,
and thus push him out, away from
the zero-gravity zone again.
And yet, you won't be able to
get away from me like that!
I'm already well aware.
Your stand's extremely powerful.
The high speed of my
rotation bullets would
easily be flicked away
as you defended yourself.
I prepared this for that reason.
I looked all over for them everywhere.
I captured them and hid them away.
There's a lot of them. Rodents!
And they're alive!
Could it possibly be?
This is...
Stone Ocean!
Flick those dirty rodents away from us!
I can't see!
There we go.
I didn't think you'd be able to push
through my zero-gravity power this much.
But you're defenseless now.
It's over.
Final blow, Jolene Kujo.
With this, my mission
is officially complete.
Jumpin' Jack Spark is the
best stand in the world.
I don't think I could
ever lose to anybody.
I'm glad to have gotten into this prison.
I've obtained enormous power here.
There may be nothing I
can't do in this world.
My future's the color
of an invincible rose.
I'm gonna hand over the disc to Palesnake.
And then defeat him too
if I deem it necessary.
I'll do it with my own hands
oh
I knew it I
was so certain you would
do it how predictable
I was just waiting for you to reload while
you were reloading your Screw bullets,
I was biding my time
with my threads flying.
And then you foolishly shot those at me.
This thread?
When in the hell did you?
Don't ocean!
Looks like you were the one who got
completely affected by the vacuum.
Also,
since you don't have a
cloud suit of your own,
your blood will boil up and
explode faster than ours will.
We've beaten you!
If you don't want to die,
then you've got to desist the
Zero Gravity Effect immediately!
That crime I committed, which got me
into this prison in the first place.
How many times did I stab that woman?
When I killed my college professor.
The prosecutor said I stabbed
that lady precisely 69 times.
This is the same feeling as then.
I feel it again after so long.
I won't forgive her
for looking down on me.
Bitch!
Add peroxide to manganese dioxide and a
chemical reaction occurs
and oxygen is produced.
Exactly like the oxygen in this
bottle, it keeps on spewing outwards.
After such a long time.
That feeling of wanting
to murder somebody.
Has come back.
You're dead.
I'll carve an epitaph into
the flesh of your corpse.
With shards of glass.
And make it reek of piss.
With those fresh cuts on your body.
Your blood will explode before mine does.
This is how your life ends, Jolene Cujo.
I got sent to this prison for stabbing
someone and I'll kill you by carving you up.
So you burst then leave this
prison have you become invincible?
I'll give mine to you.
It should be enough to
get the disc back from him
Julie it's enough, right?
What in the hell?
This is bad.
My body is also at its limit.
If I release the zero
gravity, air will flow in.
I might get away if I use that airflow.
Releasing zero gravity!
Jump in Jack Spark!
Stark!
You should have just released
zero gravity from the star.
You could have escaped from my
wrath using the wind pressure.
If you'd released it while you still had
distance between yourself and Stone Ocean.
Instead, because of your
arrogance, you waited.
Now the air is blowing you back to me!
Average for life.
For life.
How long till speed wagon gets
here? What's left? Minutes?
Seconds?
On the other side of that door
there's a passageway alongside the
right wall there are windows that
look out to the courtyard there you'll
be able to see a revolving door's
gate that's the gate to the
courtyard during daytime hours the
gate is unlocked and it's free access
but the problem is how
are we going to open
this double door i'll
have a guard open it up
We have this guy's work permit card.
I'll trick him into opening it.
I see.
Once they open this double door,
you're going to beat up any and all guards
in your path and force your way out there,
right?
Good plan.
Not only will you have the
crime of attempting escape,
but you'll also be put in
isolation for half a year.
You'll be left in a small cell
where you can't even exercise.
Doesn't matter.
I'm going to the courtyard and handing this
disc over to the Speedwagon Foundation.
Right now, it's my life's
goal and only objective.
Shh!
A guard is coming.
Listen.
Go hide somewhere over there.
I'll go on by myself from here.
Your wound is horrible.
Also, they could lock the gate right
away, if they see your blood. I get it.
You're right.
Something wrong?
Why are you hitting the door?
Oh, it's you.
He said, it's you?
Wrangler, what's wrong?
Why are you making noise?
Hold on, I'll open the door now.
Well, if you're heading back to
the men's prison, Lang Wrangler,
let's both visit the place of worship.
I'd like to speak with you.
Huh?
It's not a guard?
Who is this guy?
This man isn't a guard or a prisoner.
This person's a tire.
It's like he's a...
Of some place other than here?
Although you think I smile!
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.